## **Contact**

+971 56 1393973

🖂 calayonorman@gmail.com

# **Top Skills**

- Expertise in electronic document management systems (EDMS)
- Proficient in Microsoft Office
  Suite, particularly Microsoft Excel
- Knowledge of industry-standard document control procedures and practices
- Ability to implement and maintain document control processes and standards
- Strong understanding of change control procedures
- Knowledge of records management principles and practices
- Ability to manage electronic and hard copy records
- Excellent attention to detail
- Strong organizational and time management skills
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills
- Ability to work independently as well as in a team environment
- Familiarity with quality management systems, such as ISO 9001 or related standards
- Knowledge of project life cycle and its implications on document management
- Strong problem-solving and decision-making abilities

# **Educational Background**

#### **ACLC College**

Computer System in Network Tech.(2004 - 2005)

#### **ACLC College**

Computer System in Design and Programming (2002 - 2004)

# **Norman Calayo**

**Site Secretary / Document Controller with 10+ Years' Experience**Abu Dhabi Emirate, United Arab Emirates

#### **SUMMARY**

Over the past 10+ years, I have worked with several companies in the construction industry, specializing in documentation and clerical tasks, such as preparing correspondences, transmittals, and submittal for materials, drawings, and project reports.

I am also experienced in maintaining all register logs on a daily basis and skilled in using Electronic Document Management Systems (EDMS) such as Primavera Projects Unifier by MUSANADA, SharePoint, ORACLE Aconex, OpenText Documentum, and Etihad Rail Engineering Document Management System - Production Environment (EPFM) for data uploading.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **RAILWAY**

#### **QAQC Document Controller**

CHINA STATE CONSTRUCTION (CSCEC) / February 2020 - April 2023

As part of the QAQC Department for the Etihad Rail Project, my primary role is to manage and maintain the Test Request and Material Inspection Request.

This includes manually handling and organizing over 85,000 files for the Test Request and over 1,500 files for the Material Inspection Request. Additionally, I assist other departments and subcontractors by uploading approved documents to the EDMS application using OpenText Documentum.

#### **ROAD INFRASTRUCTURE**

#### Site Secretary / Document Controller

GHANTOOT Group / Sept. 2019 - Feb. 2020 M.A. AL-KHARAFI & SONS / Jan. 2009 - Nov.2011

As the person in charge of clerical and documentation tasks for the Internal Roads at Residential Plots in the Al Yeef - Liwa City, my responsibilities include document control, preparing correspondences, reports, and assisting with the implementation of MUSANADA's Electronic Document Management System.

Additionally, I am also responsible for physically organizing project documents for the Salam Street Project with Al-Kharafi, in addition to carrying out my clerical and documentation duties.

## **MECHANICAL, ELECTRICAL & PLUMBING SYSTEM**

#### **Site Secretary / Document Controller**

TRANS EMIRATES ELEC. & MECH. WORKS / Jan. 2016 - Aug. 2019 MABANI DELMA GENERAL CONTRACTING / Mar. 2013 - Jan. 2016

As the overall in-charge of clerical and documentation works for multiple projects with Trans Emirates, my dedication to proper documentation was put to the test and proved crucial in winning a dispute, reinforcing the importance of accurate documentation.

Similarly, my involvement in the Transmission System and Sewerage & Drainage projects with Mabani Delma emphasized the significance of maintaining an organized and disciplined approach to document control.